Solley mss., 1888-2006 LMC 2885
Lilly Library
- Automobile Catalogs
  - Italy
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa Romeo 6C 2300B 1000 Miglia"(SE: 28/1289), 1938 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa Romeo 6C 2500 Sport"(SE: 29/1290), 1939 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "La Nouvelle 6C 2500", 1948 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "La Nueva Produccion Sport", 1953 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "40 Salone...", 1953 (Oct.) (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Giulietta 50 Ans 1954-2004", c. 2004 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Giulietta 50 Ans Programme", 2004 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, Photographs (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, Renderings (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, Road Tests (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Ansaldo, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Ceirano, "Fabbrica Ceirano Automobili"(SE: 1/557), 1923 (Box 11)
    - Cistalia, "Cistalia Torino", 1947 (Box 11)
    - Cistalia, "Cistalia Torino" (slight variant of #795), 1947 (Box 11)
    - Cistalia, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "Auto-Avio Construzioni Modena..."(SE: 1/1291), 1940 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "166 Millemiglia Ferrari", 1952 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "Moderna Ferrari Italia", 1953 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "Ferrari Automobili 250 Europa...", 1955 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "250 Granturismo", 1956 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "Ferrari 365 GTB4...", 1968 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "Dino 246 GT Pininfarina", 1969 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "Dino 246 GT", 1970 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "Dino 246 GTS", 1972 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, "308 GTB 308 GTS", 1980 (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, Renderings (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, Road Tests (Box 11)
    - Ferrari, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "F.I.A.T. 8me Salon...", 1906 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "F.I.A.T.", 1906-1907 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "The Fiat"(SE: 4/241), 1913 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "Fiat Modele 510"(SE: 5/558), 1923 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "Modele 519"(SE: 6/559), 1925 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "Fiat 521", 1930 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "Fiat Mod 525n", 1930-1931 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "Fiat 500", 1937 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "Fiat 8V...", 1952-1953 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, "Fiat 8V", 1954 (Box 11)
    - Fiat, Road Tests (Box 11)
    - Fiat, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini Milano"(SE: 1/243a), 1912 (Apr. 15) (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini", 1912 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini Motors Co New York"(SE: 3/244), 1913 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini 1920"(SE: 5/560) (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "1922 Straight Eight" (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Chassis Isotta Fraschini Type 8"(SE: 6/561), 1923 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Samples of Coachwork...Straight Eight"(SE: 7/562), 1923-1924 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 8/563), 1923-1924 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 9/564a), 1924-1926 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 11/566), c. 1926 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 10/565), 1925-1927 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 12/922), c. 1928 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 14/924), c. 1929-1930 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 13/923a), 1929-1930 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 13/923b), 1929-1930 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini", c. 1929-1930 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 15/925), 1931-1932 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta-Fraschini Improvements", 1931 (Sept. 8) (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "A New 45 h.p. Isotta-Fraschini", 1931 (Sept. 11) (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Isotta Fraschini"(SE: 16/1292), 1934 (Apr.) (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Castagna 4-door"(photographs and specifications), 1937 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, "Presents its New Model 8C Monterosa", 1947 (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, Photographs (Box 11)
    - Isotta Fraschini, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Itala"(SE: 1/246), 1907 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Motore `Avalva' Sistema Itala", c. 1911 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Itala Torino"(SE: 2/247), 1914 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Modele 50 Modele 51 Sport"(SE: 3/567), c. 1923 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Modele 56..."(SE: 4/568), 1924 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Modell 61...", 1925 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Modello 61 6 Cylindri", 1926 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "6 Cylinder Itala Model 61", 1928 (Box 11)
    - Itala, "Itala 65"(SE: 5/926), c. 1928 (Box 11)
    - Itala, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Lamborghini, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia 1914" (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia 1919-1920 Chassis 35 H.P."(SE: 2/569) (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Type `Trikappa' Lancia"(SE: 4/571), 1922 (Mar. 1) (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia Tip Lambda"(SE: 6/573), 1924 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia Type Lambda"(SE: 7/574), 1925 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Curtis Automobile Co....16 H.P. Lancia Lambda"(SE: 10/927), 1927 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia Airways Saloon"(SE: 11/928), 1927 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lanica une Lambda", c. 1927 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lambda 8TE Serie"(SE: 12/929b), 1929 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia Dilambda 8 Cylinder Model"(SE: 14/931), 1930–1931 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia 'Eight'"(SE: 13/932), 1931 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Dilambda"(SE: 14/933), 1932 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia"(SE: 15/1293), 1932–1933 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Augusta, Lancia", 1935 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia, Aprilia", 1937 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia Flamina", 1959 (Box 11)
    - Lancia, "Lancia Flamina", c. 1960s (Box 11)
    - Lancia, Photographs (Box 11)
    - Lancia, Road Tests (Box 11)
    - Lancia, Misc. (Box 11)
    - Maserati, "Automobili Maserati"(SE: 1/934), 1931 (Box 12)
    - Maserati, "Maserati"(SE: 2/1299), 1935 (Box 12)
    - Maserati, "La Marca Che si Impone", 1948–1949 (Box 12)
    - Maserati, "Maserati Sport 150/S", c. 1956 (Box 12)
    - Maserati, Misc. (Box 12)
    - OM, "OM"(SE: 1/577), 1925 (Box 12)
    - OM, "The OM Cars"(SE: 2/578), 1925 (Box 12)
    - OM, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Osca, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Lancia, "Dilambda"(SE: 13/930a), 1930–1931 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Lancia, "Astura 4"(SE: 18/1296), 1937–1938 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Russia
    - ZIS, Misc. (Box 12)
  - Spain
    - Elizalde, "Automoviles 'Elizalde'"(SE: 1/580), 1917 (May 1) (Box 12)
    - Elizalde, "Automoviles 'Elizalde'"(SE: 2/581), 1919 (Oct. 1) (Box 12)
    - Elizalde, "Automoviles 'Elizalde'"(SE: 3/582), 1921 (Oct. 1) (Box 12)
    - Elizalde, "La Pratique Automobile les Chassis..."(SE: 6/585), 1923 (Box 12)
    - Elizalde, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Hispano–Suiza, "Hispanosuiza Automoviles Turismo..."(SE: 7/1300), 1933–1934 (Box 12)
    - Hispano–Suiza, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Nacional Pescara, "Nacional Pescara 110 CV Grand Sport..."(SE: 1/939), 1931 (Box 12)
    - Pegaso, "Pegaso Type 102", 1952 (Box 12)
    - Pegaso, "Pegaso", 1953 (Box 12)
    - Pegaso, "Pegaso Tipo 102", 1954 (Box 12)
    - Pegaso, "Pegaso", 1955-1956 (Box 12)
    - Pegaso, Misc. (Box 12)
  - Sweden
    - Saab, Road Tests (Box 12)
    - Volvo, Road Tests (Box 12)
    - Volvo, Misc. (Box 12)
  - Switzerland
    - Martini, "Martini: Neue Automobil..." (SE: 1/590), c. 1920 (Box 12)
    - Martini, "Martini: Neue Automobil..." (SE: 2/940), 1927 (Box 12)
    - Martini, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Piccard, "Piccard – Pictet & Cie." (SE: 1/251), 1914 (Box 12)
    - Piccard, "Piccard – Pictet & Cie." (SE: 2/591), c. 1920 (Box 12)
  - United States
    - American, "The American"(SE: 3/254), 1908 (Box 12)
    - American, "The American Underslung"(SE: 7/258), 1912 (Box 12)
    - American, "American Underslung Six Types 644 and 642"(SE: 9/260), 1914 (Box 12)
    - American, Misc. (Box 12)
    - American Mercedes, "The American Mercedes"(SE: 1/261), 1906–1907 (Box 12)
    - Apollo, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Apperson, "Apperson Motor Coaches"(SE: 2/592), 1920 (Box 12)
    - Apperson, Renderings (Box 12)
    - Arnoldt – Bristol, "Two Litre", 1958 (Box 12)
    - Arnoldt – Bristol, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "Sixes and Straight Eights"(SE: 1/942), 1927 (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "Auburn Your Next Car"(SE: 2/943), 1928 (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "Auburn Modeles 120, 8–90, 6–80"(SE: 3/944), 1929 (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "Auburn Straight Eight", 1931 (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "12 160 HP Standard...", 1933 (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "Auburn 12 Cylinder..."(SE: 4/1302), 1933 (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "1935 Auburn"(SE: 5/1303) (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "New 1936 Super–Charged Auburn"(SE: 6/1304) (Box 12)
    - Auburn, "Super–Charged Over 100 M.P.H. Auburn", 1936 (Box 12)
    - Auburn, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Baker, "Baker Electrics", 1912 (Box 12)
    - Baker, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Biddle, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Brewster, "Automobiles Brewster & Co. 1810–1922"(SE: 3/599) (Box 12)
    - Brewster, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Buffalo Electric Vehicle Co., Misc. (Box 12)
    - Buick, "New 27 h.p. Six Cylinder"(SE: 1/601), 1925 (Box 12)
    - Buick, "In the History of Motoring"(SE: 2/1306), 1933 (Box 12)
    - Buick, "The New N.A. Series Buick A"(SE: 3/1307), 1934 (Box 12)
    - Buick, "The New 'DA' Series Buick"(SE: 4/1308), 1936 (Box 12)
    - Buick, "It's a Buick Again..."(SE: 5/1309), 1937 (Box 12)
    - Buick, "Better Buy Buick"(SE: 6/1310), 1938 (Box 12)
    - Buick, "The Wonder Car of the Age"(SE: 7/1311), 1939 (Box 12)
    - Buick, "The Silver Anniversary...1904–1929", n.d. (Box 12)
    - Buick, Photographs (Box 12)
    - Buick, Renderings (Box 12)
    - Buick, Road Tests (Box 12)
    - Buick, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Automobile Company"(stationery), 1904 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Standard of the World"(SE: 2/267), 1915 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Motor Cars 1918"(SE: 3/602) (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Standard of the World"(SE: 4/603), 1921 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Motor Cars Type 61"(SE: 5/604), 1922-1923 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "A Portfolio of Cadillac Motor Cars"(SE: 6/605), 1925 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Motor Cars 90"(SE: 7/606), 1926 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac"(SE: 8/945), 1927 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac"(SE: 11/948), 1929 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "New Interpretations of Motoring Luxury", 1930 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "12 16 Multicylinder Performance"(SE: 15/952), 1931 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac La Salle", 1933 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Offers So Much More..."(SE: 21/1314), 1934 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac V-8 for 1935"(SE: 22/1315) (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Fleetwood"(SE: 23/1316), 1935 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac – La Salle – Buick..."(SE: 24/1317) (photocopy), 1935 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Fleetwood V8 – V12 – V16"(SE: 26/1319), 1937 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "The Cadillac Sixty Special"(SE: 29/1322), 1938 (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac and…Fleetwood for 1942"(SE: 33/1326) (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, Photographs (Box 12)
    - Cadillac, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Chaparral, Renderings (Box 12)
    - Chevrolet, Road Tests (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial 80 Standard..."(SE: 2/608), 1926 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Custom Built Cars"(SE: 4/9586), 1927 (November) (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Custom Cars", 1928 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial '80'", c. 1920s (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial '80' Sportif", c. 1920s (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial Eight"(SE: 7/961), 1930 (After, June) (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial Eight With Floating Power"(SE: 8/962), 1930–1931 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial Custom Eighty–Six Body Types"(facsimile), 1932 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Airflow"(SE: 11/1327), 1934 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "The New Cadillac–Fleetwood Program", 1936 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "The New Chrysler 'Super Power'"(SE: 12/1328), 1937 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, "Chryslers Thunderbolt and Newport"(SE: 13/1329a), 1941 (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, Road Tests (Box 12)
    - Chrysler, Misc. (Box 12)
    - Cord, "The Cord Front Drive"(SE: 2/966), 1930–1931 (Box 13)
    - Cord, "The New Cord"(SE: 3/1330), 1935–1936 (Box 13)
    - Cord, "The New Cord"(SE: 4/1331), 1936 (Box 13)
    - Cord, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Cumberford, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, "Cunningham Motor Cars"(SE: 1/609), c. 1919 (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, "Cunningham"(SE: 3/611), 1924 (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, "Cunningham Motor Cars"(SE: 4/612), 1925 (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, "Cunningham"(SE: 5/613), c. 1925 (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, "Fine Custom–Built Motor Cars"(SE: 6/967), 1927–1928 (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, "Cunningham"(SE: 7/968), 1929–1930 (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, Photographs (Box 13)
    - Cunningham, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Daniels Eight, "A Few Examples...", 1923 (Box 13)
    - Doble, "Doble Steam Car"(SE: 1/614), 1916 (Box 13)
    - Doble, "Doble"(SE: 2/615), c. 1924 (Box 13)
    - Doble, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, "Built to Outclass..."(SE: 1/616b) (photocopy), 1920–1921 (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, "Duesenberg – Original Straight Eight..."(SE: 2/617) (lacking plates), 1922 (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, "Duesenberg"(SE: 4/969), 1929 (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, "La Nouvelle Duesenberg 8"(SE: 6/971), 1929–1930 (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, "Duesenberg"(SE: 7/972), 1931 (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, "World's Finest Motor Car"(SE: 8/973), 1932 (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, Photographs (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, Renderings (Box 13)
    - Duesenberg, Misc. (Box 13)
    - DuPont, "DuPont Automobiles"(SE: 1/619), 1919 (Box 13)
    - DuPont, "DuPont Motors, Inc."(SE: 3/621), 1922 (Box 13)
    - DuPont, "DuPont Motor Cars"(SE: 8/976), c. 1930 (Box 13)
    - DuPont, "DuPont Motor Cars"(SE: 9/977), 1931 (Box 13)
    - DuPont, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Elcar, "Superb Elcar 8–90", 1927 (Box 13)
    - Elcar, "The New Elcar with Uno Control", 1929 (Box 13)
    - Elcar, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Fageol, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Ford, "Model T"(facsimile), c. 1908 (Box 13)
    - Ford, "...Ford Thunderbird", 1955 (Box 13)
    - Ford, Renderings (Box 13)
    - Ford, Road Tests (Box 13)
    - Ford, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Franklin 1906"(SE: 2/278) (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Franklin 1907"(SE: 3/279) (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "The Franklin Car"(SE: 7/626), 1918 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Franklin the New Series II"(SE: 8/627), 1925 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Air-Cooled Franklin"(SE: 9/979), 1928 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "New Franklin Airman Limited"(SE: 10/980), 1928–1929 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "One-Thirty-Five Franklin…"(SE: 11/981a), 1929 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Franklin Custom Coach Work"(SE: 11/981b), 1929 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Series Fifteen Transcontinental", 1931 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Series Fifteen DeLuxe", 1931 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, "Franklin 12"(SE: 16/1332), 1933 (Box 13)
    - Franklin, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Graham, Road Tests (Box 13)
    - Haynes-Apperson Company, "Motor Carriages"(SE: 3/37), c. 1900 (Box 13)
    - Haynes, "America's Greatest 'Light Six'", 1916–1917 (Box 13)
    - Haynes, "The Haynes"(SE: 5/628), 1917 (Box 13)
    - Haynes, "America's First Car"(SE: 6/629) (photocopy), 1918-1919 (Box 13)
    - Haynes, "Haynes Character Cars Sixes and Twelves"(SE: 7/630), 1920 (Box 13)
    - Haynes, "Haynes Character Cars Sixes and Twelves"(SE: 8/631), 1921 (Box 13)
    - Haynes, "The Story of Progress 1893–1922" (Box 13)
    - Hudson, "Terraplane Sixes and Hudson Eights", 1935 (Box 13)
    - Hudson, "Ride the Green Line of Safety…1939 Hudson" (Box 13)
    - Hudson, Road Tests (Box 13)
    - Hupp, "Huppmobile Motor Cars Series R", 1920 (Box 13)
    - Hupp, "New Huppmobile Series 322", 1933 (Box 13)
    - Kaiser, Road Tests (Box 13)
    - Kissel Motor Company, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Lafayette, Misc. (Box 13)
    - La Salle, "La Salle"(SE: 1/987), 1927 (Box 13)
    - La Salle, Misc. (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Book of Advanced Information..."(SE: 1/633), 1920 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars Leland–Built"(SE: 2/634), 1920 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars"(SE: 5/637), 1923 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars"(SE: 6/638), 1923-1924 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Landmarks", 1924 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Limousine Body by Fleetwood"(SE: 7/639), 1924 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Custom–Built Enclosed Cars"(SE: 8/640), 1924 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars"(SE: 10/642a), 1924 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars"(SE: 10/642b), 1925 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "The Lincoln, Special New York Salon Number"(SE: 11/643), 1924 (Oct.–Nov.) (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Custom Bodies...Chicago Salon"(SE: 9/641), 1924 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars"(SE: 13/645a), 1926 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Salon Number"(SE: 14/646), 1925 (Nov.-Dec.) (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln"(SE: 15/647), 1926 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln, Travelogue of Art..."(SE: 16/648), 1926-1927 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln,, "Lincoln"(advertising insert), 1926 (Oct. 22) (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln"(SE: 17/990), 1927 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars"(SE: 18/991b), 1927 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Salon Cars"(SE: 19/992), 1927–1928 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln", 1928 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Specification"(SE: 20/993), 1928 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "New Lincoln Body Types"(SE: 21/994), 1929 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln...Willoughby Town Sedan"(SE: 23/996c), 1929 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln...LeBaron…"(SE: 23/996d), 1929 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Motor Cars", c. 1920s (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln"(SE: 32/1005), 1932 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Twelve Cylinder Motor Cars"(SE: 30/1003), 1932 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Salon Body Types 1932" (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "The New Lincoln V–12"(SE: 35/1335), 1935 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "The Lincoln V–12 New Designs for 1936"(SE: 36/1336) (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Zephyr"(SE: 37/1337), 1936 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln–Zephyr V–12", 1936 (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln V–12 Designs for 1937"(SE: 38/1338), 1936 (Nov.) (Box 13)
    - Lincoln, "The Lincoln V-12 Designs for 1938", 1937 (Nov.) (Box 14)
    - Lincoln, "The Lincoln Designs for 1939"(SE: 40/1340) (Box 14)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Zephyr V-12 for 1940"(SE: 41/1341) (Box 14)
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Continental for 1941"(SE: 43/1343) (Box 14)
    - Lincoln, Photographs (Box 14)
    - Lincoln, Renderings (Box 14)
    - Lincoln, Road Tests (Box 14)
    - Lincoln, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Locomobile (Steam)"(photocopy), c. 1900 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Gasoline Touring Cars"(SE: 4/285), 1905 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Locomobile Book 1909" (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Locomobile 1910" (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Locomobile Book 1910"(SE: 5/286) (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Locomobile Book – The Car of 1911"(SE: 6/287) (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Locomobile Book – The Car of 1912"(SE: 7/288) (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "The Locomobile Book"(SE: 8/289), 1914 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "1916 The Book of the Locomobile 1917"(SE: 10/649) (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "Locomobile Custom Coach Work", 1917 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "The Book of the Locomobile"(SE: 11/650), 1918-1919 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "The Book of the Locomobile", 1920 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "L Locomobile"(SE: 14/653), 1925 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, "L Several Examples of Recent Coachwork..."(SE: 15/1006), 1926–1927 (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, Photographs (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, Renderings (Box 14)
    - Locomobile, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Lozier/HAL, "Lozier", 1910 (Box 14)
    - Lozier/HAL, "Lozier"(SE: 4/294), 1911 (Box 14)
    - Lozier/HAL, "Lozier Motor Cars"(SE: 6/296), 1913 (Box 14)
    - Lozier/HAL, "Lozier Motor Cars", 1916 (Box 14)
    - Lozier/HAL, "A Word to the Woman..."(SE: 7/654), 1918 (Box 14)
    - Lozier/HAL, Misc. (Box 14)
    - McFarlan, "McFarlan Six"(SE: 1/655), 1919 (Box 14)
    - McFarlan, "McFarlan Six"(SE: 2/656), 1921 (Box 14)
    - McFarlan, "McFarlan Six (Custom Built)"(SE: 3/657), 1923–1924 (Box 14)
    - McFarlan, "McFarlan"(SE: 4/658), 1926 (Box 14)
    - Marmon, "Marmon"(SE: 3/299), 1913 (Box 14)
    - Marmon, "The Foremost Fine Car"(SE: 6/661), 1922 (Box 14)
    - Marmon, "Large Marmon 75"(SE: 9/1008), 1927 (Box 14)
    - Marmon, "Great Straight–Eights", 1931 (Box 14)
    - Marmon, Renderings (Box 14)
    - Marmon, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Matheson, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Mercer, "Mercer Motor Cars"(SE: 4/303), 1913 (Box 14)
    - Mercer, "Mercer Motor Cars"(SE: 5/304), 1913 (Box 14)
    - Mercer, "Mercer Motor Cars 22–73"(SE: 6/664), 1917 (Box 14)
    - Mercer, "The Mercer"(SE: 7/665), 1922 (Box 14)
    - Mercer, Photographs (Box 14)
    - Mercer, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Mercury, Road Tests (Box 14)
    - Milburn, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Moon Motor Company, "Closed Cars for 1929 Moon–Aerotype"(SE: 6/1016) (Box 14)
    - Nash, Road Tests (Box 14)
    - Nash–Healey, Misc. (Box 14)
    - National, "National 40"(SE: 2/308), 1913 (Box 14)
    - National, "National 40 Motor Cars", 1913 (Box 14)
    - National, "National Motor Cars"(SE: 3/309), 1914 (Box 14)
    - National, "National"(SE: 4/310), 1915 (Box 14)
    - National, "National", 1916 (Box 14)
    - National, "'Highway' Twelve", 1916 (Box 14)
    - National, "Highway Twelve Cylinder Cars", 1917 (Box 14)
    - National, "Highway Cars – The Coupe...Touring Sedan", 1917 (Box 14)
    - National, "Highway Cars – Twelve and Six Cylinder Models", 1918 (Box 14)
    - Ohio Automobile Co., Misc. (Box 14)
    - Ohio Electric Car Co., Misc. (Box 14)
    - Oldfield, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Oldsmobile, "Olds Motor Works"(SE: 3/312), 1901 (Box 14)
    - Oldsmobile, "Oldsmobile"(SE: 5/314), 1904 (Box 14)
    - Oldsmobile, Road Tests (Box 14)
    - Oldsmobile, Misc. (Box 14)
    - Owen Magnetic, "The Car of a Thousand Speeds"(SE: 1/317), 1915 (Box 14)
    - Owen Magnetic, "The Car of a Thousand Speeds"(SE: 2/669) (photocopy–inc.), 1916–1917 (Box 14)
    - Owen Magnetic, "Owen Magnetic"(SE: 4/671), 1920–1921 (Box 14)
    - Packard, "Packard '30'"(SE: 8/324), 1907 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard 'Thirty,' 1908"(undated reprint) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Motor Cars 1909"(SE: 10/326) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Motor Cars 1910"(SE: 11/327), (2 copies) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Motor Cars 1911"(SE: 12/328) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard '38' 1913"(SE: 14/330) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Twin Six"(SE: 17/672a), 1916 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Twin Six"(SE: 17/672b), 1916 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Twin–Six 2–25 and 2–35"(SE: 18/673), 1917 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "The New Packard"(SE: 19/674a), 1918 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Twin–Six", 1920 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Twin–Six"(SE: 20/675b), 1920 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Twin Six"(SE: 21/676), c. 1920 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "New Packard Single–Six", 1922 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Single–Eight"First Series (SE: 22/677), 1923 (June) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Eight"Second Series (SE: 23/678), 1925 (Feb.) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Custom Built Packard Eight 236–243"(SE: 24/679b), 1925 (Late)–1926 (Aug.) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Eight – Of a Distinguished Family", 1926–1927 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Custom Built by Packard"(SE: 26/1019) (photocopy), 1926–1927 (Aug.–July) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Attributes of Packard", 1926–1927 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard De Luxe Eight 6–45", 1929 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Werner Risch Zurich", 1929 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Standard Eight 7–26...", 1930 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Custom Eight 7–40"(SE: 31/1024), 1930 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "The Speedsters by Packard"(SE: 33/1026), 1930 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Standard Eight Models 8–26 and 8–33", 1931 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "New Packard Twin Six"(photographs), 1932 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "The Packard Eight", 1933 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Eight", 1934 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Super Eight"(SE: 41/1348), 1934 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Quest for Quality...New Packard Twelve"(SE: 43/1352), 1935 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Twelve – Super Eight–Eight"(SE: 46/1353), 1936 (Box 15)